Uncle, for a long time
I lived a very long time
We have to protect good people
It's a thousand characters.
Haha, it’s a secret only I know
Captain, look at this.
Kang Woori will like it.
uh
What, I don’t even look at it properly
Oh no, I saw it. It’s pretty.
Kang Uri sleeps a lot in the winter, so we go outside.
Because it doesn't come out well
I was going to buy you one
Can't you just watch it together?
Oh yeah
You shouldn't put that on your ear.
You're looking after me
Buy it for me
I don't get along with the manager.
What's not right again?
i am now
Because of who
I've been doing this for hours
I'm watching it now
What is it
Please save me
I'll give you anything you want
I want money
Bring everything you saw today
Mr. Lee, Mr. A, you buried it, Mr. Lee.
what is this
This is how I saw it
I want to take it
Kill me first and take it.
Hehehe
Than this sloppy guy
Your bitch is so much better
Still Hanyang
There were bandits left in the land.
Then it's him
Captain, doing this and that.
Let's go. Oh no.
You will never be mine
I'll take care of it
Hold this for a moment
I'm jealous of your child
Oh yeah
I'm going to have to catch your bitch half the time.
Come on, come on, you guys
These guys
What is it
Hey, don't get hurt and just go on your way
I'm worried about you
You're sounding like I'm worried.
Just worry about yourself, you bastard.
Let's get it right
Hey
Hit it
No, everyone says I can’t do it.
We have to beat them all up.
Those damn bastards
What are you looking at? What are you doing? Take a moment.
Wow
uh
Ah ah it hurts so much
Oh, over there
It will hurt more because you have a liver.
You idiot, you keep doing such bad things
If you walk around like that
You will definitely meet me again, yeah
I'll live a good life. Get out.
Wow
Oh my, it's liver
It's okay, it's okay
No, what is this lady?
Oh, so the wind has gone out.
the wind
No, how did it fly?
Hey, I told you to stay still.
quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly
quickly quickly
quickly
quickly quickly quickly
quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly
quickly
quickly quickly quickly quickly
What's going on this night
I'm so thankful during the day
Naeun’s alcohol and
I have prepared some food
Ah
Where is the captain?
Oh boss
Marok and I are at the Sarangchae, so let’s call.
Captain, please come out for a moment.
The captain has a guest haha
For what reason
Come to work
We are that
I prepared some drinks and food.
Oh, I'm a pharmacist, but it's our heart.
please take this
Oh, we're okay.
take it and eat it
Hey, it's because we're thankful.
Please accept it out of sincerity.
Hey
W There’s some good alcohol here too.
It's a holy day, take it.
It's a bit like that, boss.
This is okay, boss.
kid then what
Thank you.
Well done haha what is this all about?
Answer quickly, I will hurt you
Come this way, let’s sleep this way.
This way, this way, please give it here.
please give it here
Wow
Ah
uh
Guys
what happened
I have to kill you
I saw it clearly with my own eyes
I like that
It must be the devil
Just out of my hand
Something strange came out.
I saw it too, I saw it too
me too
I'm sure it's the devil doing witchcraft.
With those guys
We are also part of Hwandongseongbi. Ugh.
inside
They say we have to kill all humans
Mr. We
Pretending to protect you
To deceive and reassure
Eventually that devil will kill us
You have to kill the devil first
Let's kill, kill, kill, let's kill
let's kill the baby
We have to kill the baby.
Hey
Guys, wake up.
It's okay, guys.
I guess it was drugged with alcohol.
Same
future
This is the way to go, come to your senses
Come to your senses
Now let's go somewhere
That's what humans really look like
thousands of years
Humans have always been like that since before.
while alive
twice
Never associate with humans again
thousands of years
wandered around looking for
coming
I thought I was going to die of boredom
you me
I've been searching for thousands of years
It's not that I didn't plan on waking you up.
I'm right
look at me
I also want to wake you up
I risked my life
help me
I need this power
Right with the target
angels are still alive
It's good news after a long time
It's already hard
Hey, even the beginning
What if I sit down before?
I don't want to wake up quickly
Ah
Wow
Today
I'm in really bad condition.
What's happening today
You came out for the first time today.
So, I told you to exercise regularly.
Because you want to move suddenly like this
My body doesn't listen
Don't worry, Kangji.
Well, it's half the battle
Because I warmed up today
I'll work hard starting tomorrow. Well, tomorrow.
Then why are you going already?
Hey you
I woke up early in the morning
Isn’t it a waste?
Too bad
wake up early in the morning and eat breakfast
How delicious it is to eat
Because it’s been a while since I did something
I need to eat ramen
Oh, I'm afraid the pig won't do it.
Oh my
Hey, you guys can just eat ramen too
let's go eat
You can exercise at any time.
us now
I didn't come here to eat.
Hey, why are you so talkative?
I'm nervous
You keep
You're talking nonsense.
You're sensitive because you're on an empty stomach.
So let's hit ramen
go
just go quietly
Yeah
Kangji, I'm at the convenience store over there.
Because they'll be eating ramen nearby
If you get hungry while exercising, write to me.
Okay, I'll go after the workout.
I'm enjoying it
Hey Kangji
Come quickly
Don't waste time, okay.
I'll go, see you later, uh, see you later
Hey
Oh, I told you in advance that exercise is
not labor
Let’s run a little moderately today
Don't be cruel like Soni
And when running
Take off and run
It's a nuisance because it doesn't even work
I've worn it my whole life, how can I
Is that so? I don’t know you.
Will something happen to humans?
Look, you go around thinking you’re high up.
When will the gates of hell get hurt?
Why are we in human form?
Are you living?
don't forget
Throw away bad thoughts quickly
Let's speed up
uh
Already
How much did you run?
I still have hair on my body
It was okay
run quickly
Go and receive the word in both hands.
no
Anyway, this guy
The fortune is right even on a single day
Because there is no enemy
What a lifetime of bad relationships
I've never lived in danger
I'm with the bell
There are only a million people who have been treated
I will exceed the number of people.
Hey, pay attention to what humans eat.
Don't let it in
You can live long only by eating the food over there.
Why do I eat when I’m a pig?
Listen carefully
The body fat percentage of this pig is
Thirteen percent to fifteen percent
I can't go outside
In terms of human body, it's great.
I thought he was a muscle man
What's on the pig's feet?
Yes, you insist that calluses are also muscles?
no
I am that 100% clean scaffolding
So what do you mean?
Proof that I'm not a pig
I received the power of a pig from God.
It's not a pig, it's an angel
What are the wings buried in?
Stop grunting
Just one sundae
Do you really want to stop talking nonsense?
why why
Hey there
Oh, what are you doing now?
No, he keeps telling me
You asked for sundae.
Just saying it's a pig
Yes ah what does that mean now
No, I'm over there
read minds
I have the ability to do it
Where are you talking nonsense?
You say it again, bark quickly
Oh, what is he over there?
What are you doing? Uncle, please go.
Oh really
Ah, someone else’s
What are you going to do to your dog now?
Oh, he said bullshit.
Oh, what did he say? I’m sorry.
sorry
I'm sorry. I'll apologize on your behalf.
You were very surprised
There's something wrong with this person, right?
That's it
my friend
When I'm hungry, I sometimes lose my temper. Yes.
Let's exercise
Why did you have an accident here?
I've never had an accident
Be quiet and follow me
Ahaha
You're having a good time kid.
Oh, I'm sorry.
sorry
you know my heart
If we fight with pigs, only we will lose.
You know
sorry
Ugh, I'm really lucky
The leader is involved in human affairs
I told you not to interfere.
I got involved in people's business
Because it's not true
I heard that dog started a fight first.
They say that a person from a small age is a person from a small age.
Oh no, it's not a fuss
He said he was eating ramen
Do you eat pork belly and sundae in the morning?
Well, is he the one who ate a big breakfast?
You guys, don't come into my life.
Without knowing anything
I'm going to eat all of this
without exception
In particular, I will eat all of the sundae.
Ha, you're crazy, Mr.
When you go in after chatting,
Museum before lunch
I think it will arrive
Yes, I understand.
Ah ah
I need your strength
Right with the target
angels are still alive
you are not dead
It's not like I bought it
You will be trapped in hell forever
You stopped the world by God's will
um
It's delicious. Oh, it's delicious.
They say your captain is coming out
What did you do?
Human, cheer up
They told me to pay a fair amount.
Where is our birthday yet?
It's not wrong.
captain
Except for all of us at the same time
Although I was born
That's right then
Because there was no concept of time at all.
You don't need to know
The future is
These days, I'm always working overtime because of special exhibitions.
They say it's our story
It must be our story created by humans, right?
The time we have lived is in words
That explains it.
Oh so
Who's birthday is today?
What is the bell’s birthday?
It's a civil certificate
Oh my
What the heck do I still have that?
Wow when was this
Look, I’ll see you too.
I'll change it tomorrow
Hey give it to me
Hey hey
I need to take a picture of this again.
This is like that
That countryside, Anhaknae
Go to Seoul and go to Seoul.
It's my first time taking pictures.
That's not true uh haha uh hey bells
Yeah
What do you want to stop by next year?
Why are you blinding me?
There is a good herb that will numb your tongue.
I guess you, the monkey, are any different.
Look at this
What are you looking at?
Haha hey
It's not that I hate this so much
What is it? This is okay.
This is the latest at least.
This is so crazy, what should I do?
Hey, there's more, there's more, Issi Issi
What is this?
IC
hello
You came alone
No, I saw it there
The sight of him drinking is so sexy
I'd like to have a drink with you. How about it?
ha
I'm not that dangerous person
Maybe
Do you like dogs
no alcohol on my table
There is a boy who turns into a dog when he drinks it.
Would you like to go see it together?
Go
It's a thorn
Oh, it's not that.
Hey my friend what should I do
uh
Oh, why are you like this? Why are you so stuttering?
If you look at it right away, it will come out right.
Excuse me
The lights are too bright
Should we quietly go to my house and have a drink?
Let’s go because we have a lot of expensive alcohol at home.
Let's go
The kid is good haha
All of this
They say it was all made by humans
Hey Samin
Until humans prosper like this
what the hell are you
Where did you do it?
This world
You say I should make it hell
Where did you throw away your mission?
I couldn't help it
Haetae dies
As the gates of hell close, everything
I lost my strength
Barely holding on to my life
I was looking for you
Well, what
What power does my boss have?
So
what do you want from me
the world again
full of death and curse
I need to make it hell
I need your strength to come
They say the angels are still alive
Then it's impossible even with my own strength
The angels are now powerful
I lost it and became human.
and
I love you more than now
bring great power
I'll give it to you
how
you
You can sense Haitai’s energy.
I saw it clearly
The day Taesan and his warriors killed Haetae
In the soul of the world he left behind
Find the dragon soul stones
angel and devil
The dragon that controls energy
If you breathe it into your soul
You can hatch the power of Haetae
That power
It'll be yours
But Samin
Your words are more cunning than a snake.
how can i believe
You can trust me
This is for me too
The last way to gain eternal life
Because it's an opportunity
In the end, that was the purpose
if
If you act foolishly
I'm gonna rip your head off your body
thank you
thank you child
Why did you order so much?
I don't eat
Why don't you eat it baby
Yesterday, Dalgi appeared in my dream.
sweet friends
The chickens are just hugging me
I really wanted to wear it today
I can't eat chicken
Don't talk nonsense
Anyway
Contact Samgyeopsal and Seungdae
It's like that while you're eating it
Just eat what you get
later
Don't say you're hungry while working.
Okay, but the captain
I'm working as a captain, so we can eat by ourselves.
Should I eat it all and get some takeout?
Captain, you've been a bit thin these days, huh?
Isn’t that what you said based on your standards?
I eat well alone so just leave me alone.
Captain, where did you come from?
To collect money from a used car dealer
Hey, take me with you.
Oh, those bastards
I just have to beat them all up
Just aww
But just today, I made a profit
I don't think it's a joke
Then what do you do
I don't even use it, I just wrap it up.
those difficult people
It would be great if you could help me out
Isn't it
Mmmmmmm
came out
thank you
Please wait
bridge
I would understand if you added at least one.
There are two
Well then
Well, it's crunchy.
Try this with sauce. It’s delicious.
That's right, like this
ha
Wow
Well I really like it
thirty-seven thirty-eight thirty-nine forty
Okay
If you have this much money, please just
It would be nice if you gave it to me
Why are you using a photo ID?
That's what I promised.
That's right
I don't want to put in this much effort either.
I'm sorry
The kids aren't good at fighting and
Oh, take the rest of this.
Wow, thank you
uh
Oh, it's done.
If you need money again, please contact me
I'm fine
yes
Ah
Please come in
Ah yes hello
Yes yes ah I
Also from last night
My condition is getting a little worse.
Can I come visit you today?
No, I couldn’t make a reservation in advance.
I'm out of medicine now
Yes, then we will leave right now.
yes
Hey
Teacher, Taesa has come.
yes come inside yes
Oh, you came
Oh, I ran out of medicine
I feel frustrated
I can't breathe right now
I ran out of medicine
Ah
I will start with a brief consultation.
Oh, my complexion seems to have improved a bit.
I provide consultation and management
Can you help me?
Um no
It's not helping at all.
Ah still
Because I manage it, it’s the same as before.
No, it's the same as before
Just a little bit better
no
It's not getting any better.
The disease called depression
This takes some time
I need medicine
teacher
Honestly like me
Even though it is managed by a famous doctor,
This isn't getting better
the teacher is a doctor
That means you don't trust me
Two months as usual
I'll be right over there.
Rest in peace ah
Could you please turn off the light for a moment?
This is for me too
The last way to gain eternal life
Because it's an opportunity
In the end, that was the purpose
if
If you act foolishly
I'm gonna rip your head off your body
It's not too late now
Dealing with errors
Before I even open the gates of hell
I want to die
The only way to find the Dragon Stone is in Ogi.
It's just
change the plan
um
I hate it
Maru uh
I just checked it too
me now
I'm on my way, so don't make a move first.
Okay, four floors
I'll wait
Finally, after a long journey of five months,
This is how I see the end haha
This exhibition is
Well, in the meantime
Artifacts that have not been made public
high preservation
Maybe it's because the relics were the focus.
More than ever
Many visitors
I think I was able to receive love
Haha
prepared for a long time
Our Mir team leader
And our team members
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Oh, it's probably not true, right?
Hehehe
no
Oh, that makes sense.
Suddenly, after thousands of years, you are a demon.
I talked to this guy on the phone and he said he was coming.
As for the captain, I like it.
Ah, but if this is really true
really
It's a big deal with us regular people
It's no different
How can I fight against evil spirits?
I didn't answer the phone, but I found the place.
You'll know once you get there
But will we be okay?
I'm going to get scolded by the captain.
If this is real
Is it a problem to be scolded now?
Let's go quickly first.
Yeah
What are you guys
It's the future
Guys
What are those
Oh, those are real instruments.
Ugh
Ugh uh uh
Ugh ugh
Ugh
IC
Oh, where are these guys again?
I'm just wandering around
What are you doing?
It's the future
Ah
yes
Ugh
Aha
Aha so talkative
Talkative
Ah
escape
Rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling
Even if I look back, I can't go back now
in one fist
Swinging the last with faith
flame in the dark
taishan oil
The fist that comes is a dividing knife
Even if I look back, I can't turn back
Now with a fistful of faith
wielding the last
flame in the dark
taishan oil
Blurred senses
This is a familiar illusion of tragedy
Yesterday becomes a knife that stabs me
I can't trust anyone
My heart freezes with no place to lean on
This net I have over there